Guide to the Harry Bitner papers, 1964-1975.
Bitner, Harry papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Harry Bitner papers, 1964-1975.
18-3-1892
Harry, Bitner 1916-2001
1.3 cubic ft.
Manuscripts, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes records from Cornell University on academic and administrative staff, library planning and services, and other topics; and agenda, minutes, personnel records, and other records of the South Central Research Library Council, of which Bitner was a director.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor of law, Cornell University Law School.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes records from Cornell University on academic and administrative staff, library planning and services, and other topics; and agenda, minutes, personnel records, and other records of the South Central Research Library Council, of which Bitner was a director.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Bitner, Harry,1916-2001; Cornell University.Libraries.; South Central Research Library Council.
Subjects:
Research libraries.; Academic libraries--New York (State).
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Administrative Files, 1964-1975
  - F.A.U.L., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Computing Center, 1965-1967, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Center for Improvement of Undergraduate Education, 1973, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Adn. memos - Univ., 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - C.U. L. Planning, 1972, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Economic Statues, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Ad Hoc Committees, 1970, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Continuing education, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Academic staff, 1969-1971, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Administrative staff, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ex. staff - general, 1972/1973, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Executive staff, 1969-1972, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Orientation programs - prof. and supp., 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Staff association, 1965-1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - University library grievance, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Audio visual, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Center for Research Libraries, 1965-1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Collection development, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Personnel - University library, 1965-1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Public service, 1966-1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Technical services - Univ. Library, 1969-1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Technical services - Univ. Library - Acquisitions, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Affirmative Action, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - University Library management, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - University Library - Nieneka Report, 1970, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - C.U. Libraries - academic assemblies, 1971-1974, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - [South Central Research 1975 Library Council], 1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - S.C.R.L. Council, agenda - minutes, 1974, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - S.C.R.L. Council, Board of Trustees, 1974, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - S.C.R.L. Council, By-Laws, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - S.C.R.L. Council, Planning and Advisory Committee, 1974, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - S.C.R.L. Council, Personnel, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - [S.C.R.L. Council], 1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - [S.C.R.L. Councils], 1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - S.C.R.L. Council, 1969-1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)